Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lyepez (LinkedIn) yeluis.artstation.com (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Autodesk Maya Maya Zbrush

Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Management Bootcamp Level Design Zbrush 4R7

Luis Yepez

Designer & Artist

Greater Seattle Area

Summary

3D ENVIRONMENT ARTIST / LEVEL DESIGN / WORLD BUILDING.

I am a passionate game developer with the heart of an artist and the mind of a designer. My goal is to contribute to unique polished interactive experiences that create total immersion for the players.

Technical Skills:

Modeling: Environment, Prop, Vehicle, Organic, Hard Surface, Level Design

Software:

Maya and 3ds Max, Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator, Quixel Suite, Substance Designer / Painter, UE3, UE4, Crytek, Hammer, Zbrush, Mudbox

Experience

Meta

Art Lead

December 2022 - Present (5 months)

Facebook

3D Artist

October 2021 - December 2022 (1 year 3 months)

Bellevue, Washington, United States

Undead Labs

5 years 1 month

World Design Lead

October 2018 - October 2021 (3 years 1 month)

Seattle, Washington

State of Decay 3 World and Level Design Lead

Senior World Builder

October 2016 - October 2021 (5 years 1 month)

Seattle, Washington

Hidden Path Entertainment

1 year 3 months

Lead 3D Artist

January 2016 - October 2016 (10 months)

Greater Seattle Area

Senior Artist

August 2015 - January 2016 (6 months)

*Retrofit art to run at 90fps while sprucing detail up for VR camera benefits.

*UX/UI exploration with team for modifying PC centric UI/UX into a streamlined VR experience.

*Generated new content for VR platform

5TH Cell Media

5 years 5 months

Principal Artist

August 2014 - July 2015 (1 year)

Bellevue

Senior Environment Artist

March 2010 - July 2014 (4 years 5 months)

Bellevue

SOE

4 years

Artist II SUb Lead

May 2006 - May 2010 (4 years 1 month)

Bellevue

Environment Artist

2006 - May 2010 (4 years)

Bellevue

The Art Institute of Seattle

Instructor

June 2007 - December 2008 (1 year 7 months)

Catalyst FX

FX Artist and Animator 2005 - 2005 (less than a year)

Education

Art Institute of Phoenix

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Game and Interactive Media Design · (2002 - 2005)

Uartsy

Zbrush 4r7 certification, Design and Applied Arts · (2015 - 2015)